(Sheldon:)What kind of person
leaves his keys in the car?
(Leonard:)Thought we agreed
it's Koothrappali's fault.
(Sheldon:)You're right.
(Sheldon:)Nice going.
(Scene:)Car.
(Raj:)What is wrong with people?
Why don't they stop?
(Sheldon:)Maybe we're better off.
(Sheldon:)What if we were to get in a car
with a crazy person?
(Leonard:)Look at us, Sheldon.
We're the crazy people.
(Sheldon:)Well, perhaps we should hold up a sign...
(Sheldon:)...that assures passing motorists
of our mental competence.
(Howard:)Good idea.
Why don't you get started on that?
(Leonard:)Come on, let's just start walking.
There's gotta be a gas station
or something nearby.
(Sheldon:)What, you think just because you're wearing
a captain's uniform you're in charge?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Penny:)All right.